

585 Purdue Mall ME3171, West Lafayette, IN 47907

🗷 hgchi@purdue.edu | 🏕 engineering.purdue.edu/people/hyung.gun.chi.1 | 🞧 stnoah1 | 🛅 hyung-gun | 🎓 Hyung-gun Chi

Research Interests_

My research interests lie in the fields of Computer Vision and Machine Learning. More specifically, I am interested in the Representation Learning for human action, 3D Computer Vision, and their applications in VR / AR devices and Autonomous Vehicles.

Education

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

PHD IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2023 (Expected)

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2022

• Thesis: Learning Representation for Human Action

• Advisor: Prof. Karthik Ramani

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

MS IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

· Advisor: Prof. Karthik Ramani

Yonsei University Seoul, South Korea

BS IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Mar. 2010 - Feb. 2017

· Advisor: Prof. Soo-hong Lee

• 2-year military service (2011-2013)

Research and Work Experience

Toyota Research Institute Los Altos, CA, USA

May. 2023 - Aug. 2023 RESEARCH INTERN

• Conducted human-robot interaction research (Host: Dr. Thomas Kollar).

Honda Research Institute USA San Jose, CA, USA

Jan. 2023 - May. 2023 RESEARCH INTERN

· Conducted human motion prediction research for autonomous vehicles (Host: Dr. Kwonjoon Lee).

Honda Research Institute USA San Jose, CA, USA

RESEARCH INTERN May. 2022 - Aug. 2022

· Conducted research on future action forcasting task for autonomous vehicles (Host: Dr. Chiho Choi).

Convergence Design Lab, Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT Aug. 2018 - Present

· Conducted skeleton-based human action recognition and pose estimation research (Advisor: Prof. Karthik Ramani).

HeumLabs Corporation Seoul, South Korea SOFTWARE ENGINEER & CEO Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017

• Founded and managed a start-up company as a CEO.

Developed an office automation system specifically for automating office works.

Knowledge-based Design Lab, Yonsie University Seoul, South Korea

Undergraduate Researcher Jan. 2016 - Aug. 2016

• Participated on the 3D computuer vision research (Advisor: Prof. Soo-Hong Lee).

Publications and Patents_

Journal Papers

- [J4] H. Lee, J. Lee, S. Kwon, K. Ramani, H. Chi, and D. Mun. 3D CAD Model Simplification for Mechanical Parts Using Generative Adversarial Networks. In Computer-Aided Design, under review.
- [J3] S. Kim, H. Chi and K. Ramani. Object synthesis by learning part geometry with surface and volumetric representations. In Computer-Aided Design (2021): 102932.
- [J2] S. Kim, N. Winovich, H. Chi, G. Lin, and K. Ramani. Latent transformations neural network for object view synthesis. In The Visual Computer (2019): 1-15.
- [J1] H. Hwang, S. Lee, H. Chi, N. Kang, H. Kong, J. Lu, and H. Ohk. An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification. In Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST) 33, no. 3 (2019): 1333-1339.

Preprinted papers

• S. Kim, J. Bae, H. Chi, S. Hong, B.S. Koh, and K. Ramani. Egocentric View Hand Action Recognition by Leveraging Hand Surface and Hand Grasp Type. arXiv preprint arXiv:2109.03783, 2021.

Conference Proceedings

- [C8] H. Chi, S. Chi, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. Skeleton-ODE: Learning Representation by Predicting the Future for Online Skeleton-based Action Recognition, *International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV)*, 2023. Submitted.
- [C7] S. Kim, S. Seo, H. Chi, K. Ramani, J. Kim, and S. Kim. Higher-order Relation Reasoning for Trajectory Prediction, *International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV)*, 2023. Submitted.
- [C6] H. Chi, K. Lee, N. Agarwal, K. Ramani, and C. Choi. AdamsFormer for Spatial Action Localization in the Future, In proceedings of Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023.
- [C5] Y. Xu, A. Bazarjani, H. Chi, C. Choi, and Y. Fu. Uncovering the Missing Pattern: Unified Framework Towards Trajectory Imputation and Prediction, In proceedings of Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023.
- [C4] H. Chi*, S. Chi*, S. Chan, and K. Ramani. Pose Relation Transformer: Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation, In proceedings of *IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA*), 2023.
- [C3] H. Chi*, M. Ha*, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition, In proceedings of *Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR*), 2022.
- [C2] H. Chi*, S. Kim*, X. Hu, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. A Large-scale Annotated Mechanical Components Benchmark for Classification and Retrieval Tasks with Deep Neural Networks, In proceedings of *European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV)*, 2020.
- [C1] S. Kim, H. Chi, X. Hu, A. Vegesana, and K. Ramani. First-Person View Hand Segmentation of Multi-Modal Hand Activity Video Dataset, In proceedings of *British Machine Vision Conference* (*BMVC*), 2020.

Patents

- [P5] H. Chi, K. Lee, Y. Xu, and C. Choi. System and Method for Providing Spatio-Temporal Action Localization in the Future. US Patent Application.
- [P4] Y. Xu, A. Bazarjani, H. Chi, and C. Choi. Trajectory Imputation and Prediction, US Patent Application.
- [P3] K. Ramani, H. Chi, and S. Chi. Pose Relation Transformer Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation. US Patent Application.
- [P2] K. Ramani, S. Kim, and H. Chi. Pixel-wise Hand Segmentation of Multi-modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. US Patent 11,562,489
- [P1] H. Chi. Computer Input System for Office/Factory Automation. WO Patent 2018/074729 A1.

Skills_

Research and Development Stacks Other Tools and Skills Major Languages Python, C/C++ **Text Editors** Neovim & Vim **Machine Learning** PyTorch, TensorFlow, Keras Other Langauges Shell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab(Octave), R **Web Frameworks** Django, Flask, Node.js **Operating Systems** macOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows Computer Vision OpenCV, OpenGL IDE VSCode, Eclipse, IDEA **Web Languages** Nginx, React, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS **Softwares** SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD **Database** MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, MongoDB VCS Git

Academic Activities

Reviewer

- \cdot The IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) 2023
- \cdot The IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV) 2023
- · The British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC) 2020, 2021, 2022, 2023
- The IEEE Conference on Artificial Intelligence (CAI) 2023
- · Journal of Visual Communication and Image Representation (JVCI)
- · Journal of Computing and Information Science in Engineering (JCISE)
- · Computer Vision and Image Understanding (CVIU)

Invited Talks_____

Keymuyng University	Deagu, South Korea
Guest Lecturer: Learning Representation for Human Action Recognition	Apr. 2023
Yonsei University	Seoul, South Korea
Guest Lecturer: Learning Representation for Human Action Recognition	Apr. 2023
Hongik University	Seoul, South Korea
Guest Lecturer: Learning Representation for Human Action Recognition	Dec 2022

Honors & Awards

2016	KISTI (Korea Institute of Science and Technology Information) President's Award,	Seoul. South Korea
	Edison Challenge – Computer Aided Design Section	Seoul, South Noted
2016	CDE (Korea Society for Computational Design and Engineering) President's Award,	
	CDF Challenge - Computational Design and Engineering Tools Section	Daejeon, South Korea

References_

Karthik Ramani Professor, Purdue University **Soo-Hong Lee** Professor, Yonsei University

ramani@purdue.edu shlee@yonsei.ac.kr